=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 3=
= الحلقة 3 =
Sun Weiyi.
صن ويي.
Are you trying to play dirty even in games like these?
هل تحاول أن تلعب بطريقة قذرة حتى في مثل هذه الألعاب؟
I just want
انا فقط اريد
to use the washroom.
لاستخدام الحمام.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Don't be scared.
لا تخف.
Since we have to keep each other company tonight,
بما أننا يجب أن نحافظ على بعضنا البعض الليلة ،
I'll ask and you'll answer.
سأطلب وسوف تجيب.
Okay.
تمام.
Ask me, then.
اسألني إذن.
Weiyi, have you ever loved me
وييي ، هل أحببتني من قبل
when we were a couple?
عندما كنا زوجين؟
I'll tell you the answer right now!
سأخبرك الجواب الآن!
I haven't!
ليس لدي!
I was ignorant in the past.
كنت جاهلا في الماضي.
It's because your elder sister stole my boyfriend from me.
هذا لأن أختك الكبرى سرقت مني صديقي.
I only dated you
أنا واعدتك فقط
to get back at her.
للعودة إليها.
I have never liked you.
انا لم احبك ابدا
You are truly ruthless.
أنت حقًا لا يرحم.
There's no need for you to think about them again.
ليست هناك حاجة لك للتفكير بهم مرة أخرى.
We need to learn how to be mature,
نحتاج أن نتعلم كيف نكون ناضجين ،
how to grow up,
كيف تكبر
and how to let go of the past.
وكيف نتخلى عن الماضي.
Why are you avoiding me
لماذا تتجنبني
if you're truly mature?
إذا كنت حقا ناضجة؟
♪Your determination shines on me♪
تصميمك يسطع علي
To me, everything is in the past.
بالنسبة لي ، كل شيء في الماضي.
However, to me,
ومع ذلك ، بالنسبة لي ،
our relationship has never ended.
علاقتنا لم تنته ابدا.
♪The silly smile on your face♪
♪ الابتسامة السخيفة على وجهك
♪Engraved on my heart♪
♪ محفور على قلبي ♪
Your hair still smells like gardenia.
لا تزال رائحة شعرك مثل رائحة الغردينيا.
Weiyi, you never changed
وييي ، أنت لم تتغير أبدًا
the shampoo you used.
الشامبو الذي استخدمته.
That's nice.
هذا جيد.
Bai Zeliu, please let go of me!
باي زيليو ، من فضلك اتركني!
Are you out of your mind?
هل جننت؟
♪My heart has skipped a beat♪
♪ قلبي تخطى خفقان ♪
♪Whose breathing is getting weaker?♪
♪ لمن يضعف تنفسه؟
♪I don't wish to argue who's at fault♪
♪ لا أرغب في مناقشة من هو المخطئ
♪Who can understand my feelings?♪
♪ من يستطيع فهم مشاعري؟
♪Please forgive my stubbornness♪
♪ أرجوك سامح عنادي ♪
♪The promise which was almost forgotten♪
الوعد الذي كاد أن يُنسى ♪
♪Is there something else worth waiting for?♪
♪ هل هناك شيء آخر يستحق الانتظار؟ ♪
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Tell me the truth.
أخبرني الحقيقة.
How did it go with Bai Zeliu last night?
كيف سارت الأمور مع باي زيليو الليلة الماضية؟
Did you hit a home run?
هل ضربت المنزل؟
Don't spout nonsense.
لا تتفوه بالهراء.
I just don't get it.
أنا فقط لا تحصل عليه.
Why would you fall for
لماذا تسقط ل
a miser like Ren Mingyuan?
بخيل مثل رين مينجيوان؟
(Four years ago) Hello?
(قبل أربع سنوات) مرحبًا؟
Yuanyuan,
يوانوان ،
can you lend me some money?
هل تستطيع إقراضي بعض المال؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Mr. Liu,
السيد.  ليو ،
this is Weiyi.
هذا وييي.
Could you
يمكنك
lend me some money?
اقرضني بعض المال؟
(Jiaze Computer Store) Your shoelace is tied.
(Jiaze Computer Store) رباط حذائك مقيد.
Be careful next time.
كن حذرا المرة القادمة.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Do you work as a computer purchasing agent?
هل تعمل كوكيل شراء للكمبيوتر؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I've been working the entire afternoon.
لقد كنت أعمل طوال فترة ما بعد الظهر.
But I didn't get a single customer.
لكنني لم أحصل على عميل واحد.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
I went to a tech company
ذهبت إلى شركة تكنولوجيا
when I was looking for a job.
عندما كنت أبحث عن عمل.
I heard from their HR department
سمعت من قسم الموارد البشرية لديهم
that they need a lot of them.
أنهم بحاجة إلى الكثير منهم.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Where is it?
أين هي؟
I just came to this city not long ago.
لقد جئت للتو إلى هذه المدينة منذ وقت ليس ببعيد.
I'm not really familiar with the place.
أنا لست على دراية بالمكان حقًا.
But I am.
ولكن انا.
That's great!
ذلك رائع!
He's not a miser.
إنه ليس بخيل.
He just has a budget.
لديه فقط ميزانية.
You were doing financial planning
كنت تقوم بالتخطيط المالي
over the money you spent
على المال الذي أنفقته
in your prime.
في بدايتك.
No ordinary woman can tolerate that.
لا يمكن لامرأة عادية تحمل ذلك.
Nobody is perfect.
لا أحد كامل.
We have to tolerate one another somehow.
علينا أن نتسامح مع بعضنا البعض بطريقة أو بأخرى.
You're just suppressing yourself.
أنت فقط تقمع نفسك.
By the way,
على فكرة،
I have two tickets to the opera performance.
لدي تذكرتان لأداء الأوبرا.
Do you want to join me?
هل تريد الانضمام لي؟
Q!
س!
I love you!
أحبك!
To live and die
ليعيش ويموت
for the sake of love.
من أجل الحب.
Carmen was so charming!
كانت كارمن ساحرة للغاية!
Yeah.
نعم.
It's been a long time since I've enjoyed such a wonderful performance.
لقد مر وقت طويل منذ أن استمتعت بهذا الأداء الرائع.
It feels great hanging out with me, right?
إنه شعور رائع أن تتسكع معي ، أليس كذلك؟
Let me awaken your desire.
دعني أوقظ رغبتك.
Mind your words.
مانع كلامك.
I was just afraid
كنت خائفة فقط
that you might become a boring person
قد تصبح شخصًا مملًا
and achieve nothing in life
ولا تحقق شيئًا في الحياة
after spending too much time with that blockhead of yours.
بعد قضاء الكثير من الوقت مع هذا الشخص المشهور.
Cut it out.
اقطعها.
But I have to thank you for today.
لكن علي أن أشكرك على هذا اليوم.
I didn't expect you to purchase the VIP seating.
لم أكن أتوقع منك شراء مقاعد كبار الشخصيات.
It must be expensive.
يجب أن تكون باهظة الثمن.
I'll treat you to some Japanese food next time.
سأقدم لك بعض الطعام الياباني في المرة القادمة.
Don't mention it.
لا تذكرها.
My friend gave me the tickets for free.
أعطاني صديقي التذاكر مجانًا.
It's fine as long as you're happy.
لا بأس طالما أنك سعيد.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Q,
س
the performance is over, right?
الأداء انتهى ، أليس كذلك؟
That means you've accomplished your mission.
هذا يعني أنك أنجزت مهمتك.
You may go now.
يمكنك الذهاب الآن.
Don't give yourself away.
لا تتخلى عن نفسك.
Find an excuse and leave immediately.
ابحث عن عذر وغادر على الفور.
Mr. Bai is waiting.
السيد باي ينتظر.
Understood.
مفهوم.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
My dog just ripped my sofa apart.
كلبي مزق أريكتي للتو.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
Okay, then.
حسنا إذا.
- Goodbye.
- مع السلامة.  - مع السلامة.
Weiyi, why are you walking alone
وييي ، لماذا تمشي بمفردك
in the middle of the night?
في منتصف الليل؟
I was taking a walk.
كنت اتمشى.
Don't you think
لا تعتقد
it's dangerous for a woman
إنه أمر خطير بالنسبة للمرأة
to take a walk
للتمشية
at this hour alone?
في هذه الساعة وحدها؟
As long as you don't show up,
طالما أنك لا تحضر ،
I'm safe.
انا امن.